Kurumi Tokisaki!
Wh-What's going on here?!
Nightmare!
You've finally left yourself vulnerable,
Isaac Westcott.
Ike!
Artemisia! We're falling back!
Roger!
Kurumi.
How do you do, Shido?
What seems to be the matter?
You're giving me quite the odd look.
What's the matter?
You mean you survived?
Yes, yes, thanks to you.
The moment Mio stole my Sephirah from me,
I used Het to transfer my mind
and Sephirah to a clone I created.
Of course that required quite a bit
of preparation to achieve.
Then...
You're currently a clone being possessed
by the real Kurumi's personality?
Something like that.
More importantly right now...
Zaphkiel, Dalet.
Finally, I've finally obtained it.
It's overflowing, it's overflowing...
So this is what having
a second Sephirah is like.
I feel like I can do anything now.
Kurumi, you're...
What are you...?
Shido!
Darling!
Master!
Shido!
I'm sorry we're late, Shido.
Kurumi?!
Huh?! What's going on here?!
I heard that DEM was attacking Darling?!
I took over the role of rescuing Shido.
More importantly,
it would seem an even more
troublesome foe has to come to us.
Shido, this is!
Mio!
Yes. I'm sorry, Shin.
I still have much to learn,
letting myself fall for that diversion.
Though I'm glad you're safe.
I thank you too, Kurumi.
You protected Shin for me.
My, my, hearing thanks from you
only brings up awful memories.
Shido!
Mio is after you!
So run away while we buy you some time!
It's futile.
Shin and I already share a connection.
I know what Shin experienced in the future, too.
His means of returning to the past
won't work anymore.
Shido?!
Stop, she's dangerous.
Mio.
Shin.
I couldn't seal away your Spirit power.
You were in a half-state
without all the Sephirah, after all.
But I know that wasn't the only reason.
I have to kiss a Spirit
after she opens her heart to me
in order to seal her Spirit power.
But you still haven't opened your heart to me.
Shin?
What do you mean?
In that moment her affection
was definitely high enough to seal her.
You're wrong.
Huh?
You've got it wrong.
The one Mio loves isn't me.
It's Shin. Shinji Takamiya.
And...
Shinji is no more.
What are you saying, Shin?
That's why I recreated you.
I even granted you the power of Spirits
so you would never die this time.
Yeah, your power truly is amazing.
But even if I gathered all of the Sephirah,
and all of my memories
as Shido Itsuka vanished from my mind...
would I really be Shinji?
I would be a person that looks like Shinji
and possesses Shinji's memories,
but that wouldn't be Shinji.
Shinji's soul wouldn't be there.
I'm betting you already
understand that all too well.
You understand that,
and yet you can't help but cling to it.
Though would that truly
satisfy your heart, Mio?
Why are you saying these things, Shin?
You're all I have, Shin.
I've lived my entire life
to see you once again, Shin.
Cut the crap!
You have me!
And you have all the Spirits, don't you?!
Is the time we all spent together that
inferior to the time you spent with Shinji?
Oh, I get it.
You're saying these things
because you're not Shin.
I need to hurry and get Shin back.
Thank you for everything, Shido.
But...
It's time for our farewell.
Sandalphon!
Thanks, you saved me!
Don't mention it!
Though what do we do now?
I'm going to kiss Mio again.
Hmm?
What are you saying?!
You're the one who just said she
didn't have enough affection for you!
Which is why this time, I have to make her
choose me, Shido Itsuka, instead of Shinji!
Otherwise, I'm sure Mio will...
Kurumi!
That was a close call, wasn't it?
This position is a little embarrassing...
Now isn't the time to be discussing that.
More importantly, that's an
amusing idea you just proposed.
Kissing Mio once again.
Yeah, and I plan to.
You already failed
to seal her once, didn't you?
Do you have any chance of succeeding this time?
Is that Mio's true desire?
Are you saying that's the reason
she turned all of us into Spirits?!
Yeah.
I'm fairly certain of it.
Shido.
There's no means of escape
once we're trapped in this space, right?
And since Mio shares your memories,
she should be able to stop Zaphkiel's
ability to travel back in time as well.
Which means
we'll need to bet on the possibility
with the greatest chances for survival.
I've done this much for you already.
Now be sure you see this through.
Yeah.
Thanks, Kurumi.
My, my, you've become
awfully good at this, Shido.
My body feels light.
My entire body is brimming with power.
I see. Now I truly have the power
of all 10 Sephirah within me.
Now I can pull this off!
Shin!
Shido!
Boy!
Brother!
Master!
Darling!
Ike!
Ike, are you all right?
So that is what it feels like to have
a Qlipha yanked out while still alive.
That was a valuable experience.
Is this any time for jokes?!
What's the situation?
It seems Nightmare has entrusted
her power to Shido Itsuka.
And Goetia?
It's still next to Fraxinus.
Remote control hasn't been cut off.
I see.
Then all is going smoothly, right?
Kotori!
Are you all right?!
Yes, I wasn't injured.
I just hit my time limit.
More importantly...
What's this?
Perplexed. What is happening here?
Kotori, Shido is safe, right?
Of course.
Shido wouldn't go down
from something like this.
Yeah, you're right.
Nia, can you hear me?
Bring the monitoring equipment here.
Analyzing
Complete
Mmn, it's no use.
No way!
Nia, please leave this part to me.
Kurumin!
Raziel!
That's possible?!
I mean, well,
I guess it would be after that villainous
president took my Sephirah, but still-
Quiet.
It's my first time using this Angel,
so please let me focus.
Ngh, I'm getting NTR'd?!
So humiliating!
Can you tell how Shido's doing?
Yes.
It seems he's safe.
What's this?
Right!
Where is everyone?!
Shin.
R-Reine?!
Wh-What's going on here?!
Where is everyone?
Where's Fraxinus?
Give me your hand.
Huh?
S-Sure.
Thank you.
Hey! Here, over here!
Huh?
Mio?
And...?
M-Me?
No, it's not.
You're...
Shin?
Shinji Takamiya?
Yeah.
I guess I should say nice to meet you?
What is this...?
It would seem to be a space created by Ein Sof.
It seems to be?
There's a connection between you and me.
It seems like our shared memories
are being recreated through that.
In doing so, I think it separated our minds
into me and Mio plus you and Shin,
in order to create a state
more closely resembling those memories.
I-I see?
Isn't this kind of thing nice?
More importantly, let's have fun?
Since we're at the beach and all.
You've done it now!
Take that!
Are you losing the sense that you were Shin?
Huh?! Can you read my mind in this space?!
That wasn't it.
I just figured you were like myself.
Huh?
I suppose the emotions I held as Mio
might have gone into that Mio
when our existences were separated.
It's a strange feeling.
It really feels like I'm Reine Murasame,
a separate person from Mio Takamiya.
Reine...
It really feels nice, doesn't it?
I should thank you for bringing me here, Shin.
I'm just glad you're enjoying it.
I worked pretty hard to find
a place with nice scenery.
Shido.
I'm all right.
Oh, I wanted to try that! Those fireworks!
You have to light fireworks
when you visit the beach, right?
We were home by evening last time
we came here, so we couldn't do it.
I-I couldn't help it.
We had to leave by then
or it would've gotten too late,
and we would've worried Mana,
as well as give people the wrong idea.
That just means there's more fun
to be had in the future, right?
I want to try diving and having a barbecue, too.
Let's try out lots and lots more things?
I'm sure it'll be fun with you,
me, Reine, and Shido!
I honestly wish this time could last forever.
Yeah, that's true.
But nothing lasts forever.
Isn't that right, Mio?
Mio.
I'm sorry.
I made you say that, didn't I?
When I first kissed Reine,
your memories as Mio flowed into me.
I couldn't understand what they were,
and I didn't understand what they meant,
but...
Now I finally...
I finally understand.
Mio.
You gave birth to me in order to
bring the dead Shinji back to life.
Isn't that right?
But that wasn't all.
Because you knew the Shinji created
that way wouldn't be the real Shinji.
I'm not sure if you were
conscious of it or not,
but after seeing your memories,
I learned something.
Mio, you gave birth to me
to create a being that could kill you.
How is it, Kurumi?!
On the shore there's Shido, Mio,
Ms. Murasame, and another Shido?
Hmm? Did you say there are two of Master?
That's strange.
Also, Mio and Reine are separated?
Suspicious. Was that cocoon
capable of reproduction?
I won't know without looking into it.
Why did they end up like that?
Wh-What?!
An extremely strong spirit wave.
But where did it come from?
Everyone, over there!
Origami!
Mana!
They're definitely plotting something!
I'll go eliminate them!
Metatron!
It's no use.
The spell has already been activated.
I'm sorry.
Looks like this is the end.
Yes, I believed in you, Shido Itsuka.
I knew you would surely stop Deus for me.
Rejoice, everyone!
You all get to witness the birth
of a second Spirit of Origin!
Episode 11
A Fleeting Paradise
Episode 12: "And The One She Chooses Is"
The time to settle things has finally arrived.
What conclusion will the love
between Shinji, Mio, and Shido lead to?
The final episode,
"And The One She Chooses Is".
Now, let's head out on our last date.